Okay, so I’m here today at Bristol.
My love affair with Bristol started in 2018,
and it’s been a very beautiful relationship since.
I’ve been to Bristol several times over the last six years.
And one of the things that I love about Bristol is that the work it’s done
over the last six years has been hugely influential.
Not only in the space of intersectionality, broadly speaking,
and race, specifically speaking,
it’s been a really great exemplar for other institutions in the locality
and further on in the sector
in terms of the amazing work they’ve done in areas like decolonising the curriculum,
thinking about better employment interventions for black and ethnic minority staff,
looking at its promotion and progressions,
thinking about how it diversifies its student body and staff body.
So there’s been some really good interventions that have happened
and also staff becoming more literate around
Black history and Black British history in particular
So being part of some of those interventions over the last couple of years
and working with the ED and I team
and working with kind of academics of the like at Bristol has been hugely influential.
And yeah I think this is the 15th or 16th time I’ve been here in six years.
It really, really means a lot.
So thank you so much for having me here today.
And yeah, it’s a blast. I love this place.
My home away from home.
And yeah, I probably at some point I probably should have worked here at some point during my career.
I’ve been here that many times, but it might happen one day.
So thank you so much.
Really appreciate being here today.